In academic texts, we also make point lineups.
It may be for slightly different reasons
but above all if you want to do things clear-
or when you want to highlight specific things-
Or when you want to clarify things.
But when should you make setups
And not reproduce the information in your body text?
There are some guidelines to follow.
They look like this:
When you want to emphasize some information.
When a sentence contains long enumerations.
When you want to explain or sort out complicated facts.
All this is about facilitating reading.
If you need to make a point lineup, there are guidelines to follow.
You have to be careful about how to construct your joints in your set up.
You should construct them similarly in both form and content.
You can formulate your points in slightly different ways.
For example, your joints may be focused on words or phrase
on a sent-
or one or more sentences.
But...
You must be careful not to mix the way you write your joints.
Namely
You must not mix individual words with complete sentences.
You choose a way
to formulate yourself in your set -up.
If you are going to make a point lineup with short joints
Has each joint lowercase.
It may look like this.
"In the first place you can seek answers by"
"Read your course literature, visit your nearest library, talk to a student friend."
Then it will be with a colon.
But is it not an independent batch
it will not be the colon.
It depends on how you have built up your meaning structure.
Your joints can be marked in slightly different ways.
You can use point, tank line, letters (common) or numbers.
When you write with numbers it may look like this.
You have 1.2 and 3 and always a point after.
Letters have a final bracket behind it.
Would you like to refer to your point lineup further in your body text
Then 1, 2 and 3, or A, B and C are best to use.
It is not possible to refer back to point or tank line.
Would you like to comment on your points
Do you use any of these.
You can also use both of these.
For example, if you have a first joint with numbers
and wants to during e.g.
the third-
You can refer to both numbers or letters further in your text
If you want to comment on what is in the point lineup.
So...
Consider when using point set up.
Make sure you are constructing similarly.
Formalia and punctuation you must follow
So as I went through in this movie.
Make sure to use point set up to increase readability in your text.
So have you made point lineups
Look how they look.
Fix what may need to be addressed.